(Raj:)...thank you very much.
(Amy:)Gentlemen,
the game offers us a choice...
(Sheldon:)...between playing for the Republic
and the light side...
(Sheldon:)...or the Sith Empire and the dark side.
(Leonard:)We're always the good guys.
ln "D&D" we're lawful good.
ln "City of Heroes" we're heroes.
ln "Grand Theft Auto"...
(Leonard:)...we pay the prostitutes promptly
and never hit them with a bat.
(Sheldon:)Those women are prostitutes?
(Sheldon:)You said they were raising money
for stem-cell research.
(Howard:)Hey, guys. I got a surprise.
Mm, if it's yogurt that helps ladies poop,
l think Raj beat you to it.
No, Bernadette's gonna be playing with us.
(Howard:)So that's pretty cool, huh?
Right? Sure, it is.
Wha?... You invited your girIfriend?
(Raj:)- This is supposed to be our weekend.
- l had no choice.
She said, "Why don't we go out
for brunch and maybe the arboretum?"
l said, "No, I promised the guys I was
gonna play a video game with them."
She said, "Can I come?"
Then I didn't answer for a second.